ARKADIY KOLOMIETS

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I'm a developer with experience in a blockchain-oriented development company. I'm passionate about learning new technology and programming languages. I'm looking forward to taking part in developing the apps that will make this world a better place.

Despite the fact that I am only at the beginning of my journey as a developer, in the near future, I see myself in the position of a Full Stack Web Developer, ready to fully manage projects. My goal in a few years is to grow to the CTO position of a company.

SKILLS

- Back-end programming languages: Python
- Back-End Framework: Django, Django REST framework, Flask, NodeJS
- Front-end programming languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript
- Front-End Framework: Angular, React, Redux, Redux Toolkit
- Design tools: Material-UI, Angular Material UI, SaSS, Bootstrap 5, Figma
- Database: Firebase, SQLite, MySQL, SQL-Server, MongoDB
- Development tools: Docker

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

IdeaSoft | Jun 2021 - Present (1 year, 6 months)

IdeaSoft is a custom software development company. In 2021, the company became part of Sigma Software Group.

- Wrote and tested code, debugged programs, and integrated applications with third-party web services by using Python Django and Django REST Framework
- Using MongoDB and SQL-Server databases in development
- Developed new features by using JavaScript, React, and Redux
- Developed UI for applications by HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Material-UI, Bootstrap 5 and Figma

EDUCATOR

Leo Baeck Elementary School Haifa | Oct 2019 - Jun 2020 (10 months)

RESCUE INSTRUCTOR

IDF - Search and Rescue Brigade | Mar 2018 - Sep 2019 (1 year, 6 months)

YOUTH PROGRAM COORDINATOR

The Jewish Agency for Israel | Aug 2015 - Jun 2018 (2 years, 6 months)

CONTACT

in arkadiy-kolomiets

Ar1kol

1 050-302-2237

✓ arielkolomiets@gmail.com

EDUCATION

2021 - 2022

John Bryce - Haifa

Python Full Stack Development

2020 - 2021

SOURCE IT

Introduction to Web Development

2011 - 2014

Omsk College of Construction and Transport Industry Technologies

Bachelor of Operation of transporttechnological machines and systems

INTERESTS

- Sport gym and running
- Travel
- Helping people volunteer
- Art visiting exhibitions and workshops